(gasps)
There's Amy.
(Sheldon:)I just know
you're gonna hit it off.
(Sheldon:)You both have
the same fashion sense.
Hello! Come in,
say hi to my Meemaw.
(Amy:)Hi. Nice to meet you.
(Meemaw:)Nice to meet you, too.
(Amy:)How was your trip?
(Meemaw:)Wonderful.
(Meemaw:)And the pilot did
such a good job,
(Meemaw:)I gave him a butterscotch.
(laughs)
That's great.
(Amy:)And look at you,
sitting in Sheldon's spot.
(Amy:)You know, I don't
even get to sit there.
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)And you never will.
(Sheldon:)Ooh, hey, oh, ask her to do the
tissue thing.
(Sheldon:)Do it, ask her.
(Amy:)Can I have a tissue?
(Meemaw:)Of course.
(laughs)
Isn't that the best?!
(Sheldon:)She's like Grandma Spider-Man.
(Meemaw:)He's been saying that
(Meemaw:)since he was little.
(Meemaw:)I still don't know
what it means.
(Sheldon:)Oh, well, you two sit down
and get to know each other.
(Sheldon:)I'll get your room ready.
(Meemaw:)Oh, now don't you go
looking through
(Meemaw:)my suitcase for presents.
(Sheldon:)If I did, would I find any?
(Meemaw:)Maybe.
(Meemaw:)But you also might find
my brassieres and bloomers.